Suraj Shahi

+977-9868229079

surajshahi331@gmail.com

https://www.linkedin.com/in/suraj-shahi-455b7a206/

Summary

I have over 2.5 years of experience in web development and am proficient in HTML5, CSS3, JS, Bootstrap, Tailwind CSS, and Webflow. I have gained valuable experience through years of working and I have a strong knowledge of creating web applications that are responsive and user-friendly.

Experiences

Rapid Web Solution Pvt. Ltd, Kathmandu

Markup/Frontend Developer

Aug 2021 - Present

- Creating a stunning website as per a client's request.
- Reporting to the manager, logging time on Jira, and collaborating with other team members.
- Reading Client notes carefully so I don't miss any things during the development process
- Never exceed the deadlines, fix bugs, and after completion of the project work on feedback and update whenever necessary.
- Consulting with the senior developer in case of confusion regarding the tasks and giving the best optimal suggestions to the client whenever I feel necessary.

Broadway Infosys, Kathmandu

Web development traning

April 2021 - July 2021

Codewing Solution Pvt. Ltd, Kathmandu

UI/UX Intern

Jan 2021 - April 2021

Education

Bachelor in BSC.CSIT

Central Campus of Science and Technology, Mid-Western University, Surkhet

Oct 2016 - Nov 2020

Tools

Frontend tools

- HTML5/CSS3/JS
- Responsive design
- Semantic HTML
- Bootstrap
- Tailwind
- WebflowGsap

Design tools

- Figma
- XD
- Photoshop
- Illustrator

Development tools

- NPM
- WEBPACK
- VITE

Soft Skills

Languages

Nepali

Fluent

English

Conversational

Personal skills

- Time-management
- Organization
- Decision making
- Collaboration
- Adaptability

Useful Links

https://www.behance.net/surajshahi1

https://github.com/suraj-irukaht

https://codepen.io/suraj-shahi

Currently Learning

- React JS
- Javascript
- Wordpress